<resources>
    <string name="app_name">PreschoolScheduleMaker</string>
    <string name="long_string">Why does my Android emulator look wrong? - Stack Overflowstackoverflow.com › questions › why-does-my-android... Nov 18, 2016 — You need to download and run Visual Studio Emulator for Android, then ... You should use an AVD Device Template to get a normal size:. 3 answers Android studio emulator displaying screen wrongly ... 1 answer Apr 24, 2017 Emulator wrong screen resolution in Android Studio ... 1 answer Aug 26, 2015 Android emulator uses wrong layout resources ... 1 answer Dec 3, 2015 Android emulator screen fills up only some fraction ... 13 answers Aug 1, 2017 More results from stackoverflow.com Troubleshooting and known issues for Android Emulator and ...developer.android.com › studio › run › emulator-troub... Aug 25, 2020 — If your machine has both an Intel HD 4000 GPU and a discrete GPU, disable the Intel HD 4000 GPU in Device Manager to ensure you are using ... Run apps on the Android Emulator | Android Developersdeveloper.android.com › studio › run › emulator Oct 12, 2020 — The Android Emulator simulates Android devices on your computer so that you can ... To run the emulator in Android Studio, make sure you\'re using Android ... If this setting is incorrect, features such as screenshot capture and ... Android Emulator Troubleshooting - Xamarin | Microsoft Docsdocs.microsoft.com › ... › Android Emulator Setup Aug 27, 2018 — Launch the emulator from the Android Device Manager (select your virtual ... If the virtual device you are running in the emulator does not have ... virtualization technologies, incorrect settings, or an out-of-date HAXM driver. Managing Virtual Devices with the Android Device Manager ...docs.microsoft.com › ... › Android Emulator Setup Jan 22, 2019 — This article explains how to use the Android Device Manager to create ... You use the Android Device Manager to create and configure Android Virtual Devices (AVDs) that run in the Android Emulator. ... This makes it possible to run and test your app in a variety of ... Wrong Version of Android SDK Tools. Top 10 Most Common Mistakes That Android Developers Makewww.toptal.com › android › top-10-most-common-and... Don\'t get me wrong, I\'m not an Android programming evangelist! I respect ... The Android Emulator is super good in replicating physical devices. Even better, try ...</string>
</resources>